Guide to the Frank Moore Papers MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Source Material
  - Subseries G: Books
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 18, Folder 837)
    - Dowden, Anne Ophelia The Secret Life of the Flowers, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 838)
    - de Duve, Christian A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 839)
    - Eisenberg, Jerome M. A Collector's Guide to Seashells of the World (Box 18, Folder 840)
    - Ellenberger, W. An Atlas of Animal Anatomy for Artists annotated, undated (Box 18, Folder 841)
    - Ellis, Richard Aquagenesis: The Origin and Evolution of LIfe in the Sea, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 842)
    - Faideau, F. La Botanique Amusante, undated (Box 18, Folder 843)
    - Fodor's National Parks of the West. annotated, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 844)
    - Foshay, Ella M. and Sally Mills. Nineteenth Century American Landscapes, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 845)
    - Fox, Derek Lilies, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 846)
    - Free, John Bees and Mankind, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 847)
    - von Frisch, Karl. The Dance Language and Orientation of Bees, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 848)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 18, Folder 849)
    - Goody, Jack. The Culture of Flowers, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 850)
    - Gourlay, K.A. World of Waste, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 851)
    - Grafton, Carol Belanger Accents and Attention-Getters, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 852)
    - Grafton, Carol Belanger Borders on Layout Grids, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 853)
    - Graham, Frank. The Adirondack Park., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 854)
    - Greenberg, Jerry. Fish, Men, Fear...Shark!, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 855)
    - Grehan, Farrell and H.W. Rickett The Odyssey Book of American Wildflowers, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 856)
    - Guptill, Arthur L. Norman Rockwell, Illustrator, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 857)
    - Hargreaves, Dorothy and Bob Tropical Blossoms of the Caribbean, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 858)
    - Hennessey, Maureen Hart and Anne Knutson Norman Rockwell: Pictures for the American People, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 860)
    - Hornung, Clarence P. The American Eagle in Art and Design, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 861)
    - Huelsen, Walter Sweet Corn, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 862)
    - Instruments de Torture et de Mort a Travers les Ages, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 863)
    - Kepes, Gyorgy Structure in Art and in Science, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 864)
    - Klossowski de Rola, Stanislas Alchemy, The Secret Art, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 865)
    - Klots, Alexander B. A Field Guide to Butterflies, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 866)
    - Klots, Alexander B. and Elsie B. Klots Living Insects of the World, undated (Box 19, Folder 867)
    - Kohler, Carl A History of Costume, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 868)
    - Krutch, Joseph Wood The Garderner's World, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 869)
    - Leeson, Tom and Pat The American Eagle, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 870)
    - Lindauer, Martin Communication Among Social Bees, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 871)
    - Maeterlinck, Maurice La Vie des Abeilles, undated (Box 20, Folder 872)
    - Manahan, Stanley E. Environmental Chemistry, 5th edition, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 873)
    - Mathis, Maurice L'Exploitation Rationnelle des Abeilles, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 874)
    - McCracken, Harold George Catlin and the Old Frontier, undated (Box 20, Folder 875)
    - Mellon, James The Face of Lincon, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 876)
    - Mendoza, George Norman Rockwell's Americana ABC, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 877)
    - Menten, Ted Decorative Corners, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 878)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art Gardens as Illustrated in Prints, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 879)
    - Michelmore, Susan Sexual Reproduction, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 880)
    - Mitchell, Paul and Lynn Roberts Frameworks: For, Function and Ornament in European Portrait Frames, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 881)
    - Morcombe, M.K. Wild Australia, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 882)
    - Musee Du Louvre Technique de la Peinture l'atelier, with annotations, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 883)
    - Museum of Modern Art, New York Jasper Johns, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 884)
    - Museum of Modern Art, New York The Natural Paradise, Painting in America 1800-1950, with annotations, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 885)
    - national Geographic Society Wondrous World of Fishes, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 886)
    - Niagara- River of Fame, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 887)
    - Nicholas, Jeff and Lyn and Jim Wilson Wildflowers of Yosemite, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 888)
    - Pain, Nesta Lesser Worlds: The Fascinating Story of Life in the Strange World of Insects, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 889)
    - Parker, W. Oren and Harvey K. Smith Scene Design and Stage Lighting, with annotations, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 890)
    - Peterson, Roger Troy A Field Guide to the Birds, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 891)
    - Poole, Lynn and Gray Weird and Wonderful Ants, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 892)
    - Preston-Mafham, Ken Grasshoppers and Mantids of the World, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 892)
    - Rogers, Julia Ellen The Shell Book, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 893)
    - Root, A.I. ABC and XYZ of Bee Culture, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 894)
    - Runte, Alfred Yosemite, THe Embattled Wilderness, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 895)
    - Schneider, Paul The Adirondacks, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 896)
    - Seibel, George A. Ontario's Niagara Parks, with annotations, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 897)
    - Serpa, Louise and Larry McMurtry Rodeo, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 898)
    - Sheldom, William H. Atlas of Men: A Guide for Somatotyping the Adult Male at all Ages., 1954 (Box 22, Folder 899)
    - Simon, Jacob The Art of the Picture Frame. Artists, Patrons and the Framing of Portraits in Britain, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 900)
    - Simonelli, Jeanne and Charles Winters Too Wet to Plow, with annotations, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 901)
    - Singer, Sam Human Genetics, An Introduction to the Principles of Heredity. 2nd edition, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 902)
    - Sontag, Susan Illness as Metaphor and AIDS and its Metaphors, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 903)
    - Swain, Ralph B. The Insect Guide, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 904)
    - Swift, Jonathan Gulliver's Travels, with annotations, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 905)
    - Tales of the Great Lakes: Stories from Illinois, Michigan, Minnesota and Wisconsin., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 906)
    - Time Life Television Wild, Wild World of Animals Insects and Spiders, with annotations, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 907)
    - United States Department of Agriculture Insects. The Yearbook of Agriculture, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 908)
    - Versace, Gianni Rock and Royalty, with annotations, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 909)
    - Vroman, Leo Blood, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 910)
    - Waldrop, M. Mitchell Complexity: The Emerging Science at the Edge of Order and Chaos, with annotations, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 910)
    - Wilson, Alexander The Culture of Nature: North American Landscape from Disney to the Exxon Valdez, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 911)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 912)
    - Wyckoff, Jerome The Story of Geology, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 913)
- Series V: Beehive
  Series V includes all materials from the production of Frank Moore and Jim Self's collaborative film "Beehive" as well as the Boston Ballet production. The series is divided into eight subseries containing the film, video and audio production elements, technical notations and lab related paperwork, production materials corresponding to the Beehive film, production materials corresponding to Beehive the ballet, promotional materials, artifacts, as well as film and video preservation elements and access copies. Subseries A Film and subseries B: technical notations and lab related paperwork are organized chronologically by unique object identification number. Subseries C: Production materials Beehive film, D: Production materials Beehive Ballet, E: Promotional materials and F: Artifacts are organized alphabetically. Subseries G: Preservation elements - film and video and H: Access copies - film and video are organized numerically by unique object identification number.
  - Subseries A: Production Elements
    - Film Production Elements: 16mm and 35mm negative, 16mm mag track, 16mm and 35mm workprint, 16mm and 35mm answer print, 1982-1986 (Box not specified, Folder 135.0009-135.0132)
    - Film Production Elements, 1982-1986 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 135.0135)
    - Film Production Elements, 1982-1986 (Box not specified, Folder 135.0139-135.0155)
    - Film Production Elements, 1982-1986 (Box not specified, Folder 135.0163-135.0165)
    - Video Production Element: Beehive Work Print, early 1980s; ID: 135.0001 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0001)
      General
      Video Recording, Scotch T-60 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Beehive -- Selected Takes [Film Transfer Master], 1/26/84; ID: 135.0002 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0002)
      Video Recording, [15:04] UCA-15 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: [Beehive Beta], late 1970s - early 1980s; ID: 135.0003 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0003)
      Video Recording, L500 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Beehive Animation Exp., [undated]; ID: 135.0004 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0004)
      Video Recording, UCA-20 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Beehive Excerpts, 1985 Angers Production, Dub by Frank Moore and Jim Self, ID: 135.0156 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0156)
      Video Recording, [60:00] Hitachi E-60 Video Cassette. See Series G for digital access copy.
    - Video Production Element: Beehive Cornell '91, Rough Rehearsal, 1991; ID: 135.0157 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0157)
      Video Recording, [02:00:00] T-120 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "Beehive" copy 1, [undated]; ID: 135.0158 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0158)
      Video Recording, [30:00], TDK Super Alvyn High Standard HS T120 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Primary Performance Group, Inc., "Beehive Ballet", 1988; ID: 135.0159 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0159)
      Video Recording, [02:00:00], Kodak Video Cassette, See Series G for digital access copy.
    - Video Production Element: Primary Performance Group "Beehive 1985" [Audio - 2 TRK Mono], ID: 135.0160 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0160)
      Video Recording, [20:00], Sony 20 BRS Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Beehive Glasses Tape 1, [undated]; ID: 135.0161 (Box 23A, Media ID: 135.0161)
      Video Recording, [20:00], UCA 20 Video Cassette
    - Audio Production Elements: 1/4" reel to reel, 1982-1983 (Box 23C, Folder ID: 135.0005-135.0008)
    - Audio Production Elements, 1982-1983 (Box 23C, Folder ID: 135.0180)
    - Second Beehive Workprint, circa 1980s (Box 70, Vhs 135.0263)
    - Beehive Ballet (Cornell Production), Spring 1991 (Box 70, Vhs 125.0264)
    - Frank Moore/Primary Performance Group: Beehive 1985 (Box 70, Vhs 135.0265)
  - Subseries B: Technical notations and lab related paperwork
    - 135.009A-135-0011A. Work order, timing strips, printing and negative cleaning documentation., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 914)
    - 135.0009A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 914A)
    - 135.0010A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 914B)
    - 135.0011A Edge number note., undated (Box 23, Folder 914C)
    - 135.0012A-135.0015A. Timing strips, lab order, printing and cleaning report documentation., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 915)
    - 135.0012A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 915A)
    - 135.0013A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 915B)
    - 135.0014A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 915C)
    - 135.0015A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 915)
    - 135.0016A-135.0022A. Work order, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 916)
    - 135.0016A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916A)
    - 135.0017A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916B)
    - 135.0018A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916C)
    - 135.0019A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916)
    - 135.0020A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916E)
    - 135.0021A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916)
    - 135.0022A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 916G)
    - 135.0023A-135.0031A. Work order, timing strip, printing and negative cleaning report., 1983 (Box 23, Folder 917)
    - 135.0023A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917A)
    - 135.0024A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917B)
    - 135.0025A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917C)
    - 135.0026A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917)
    - 135.0027A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917E)
    - 135.0028A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917)
    - 135.0029A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917G)
    - 135.0030A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917H)
    - 135.0031A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 917I)
    - 135.0032A-135.0037A. Lab order, timing strip, packing slip, negative cleaning report, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 918)
    - 135.0032A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918A)
    - 135.0033A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918B)
    - 135.0034A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918C)
    - 135.0035A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918)
    - 135.0036A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918E)
    - 135.0037A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 918)
    - 135.0043A-135.0047A. Timing strip, work order, printing and negative cleaning report, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 919)
    - 135.0048A-0054A. Work order, timing strip, printing and negative cleaning report., 1983 (Box 23, Folder 920)
    - 135.0048A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920A)
    - 135.0049A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920B)
    - 135.0050A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920C)
    - 135.0051A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920)
    - 135.0052A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920E)
    - 135.0053A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920)
    - 135.0054A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 920G)
    - 135.0055A-135.0060A. Timer's listing, timing strip, printing and negative cleaning report, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 921)
    - 135.0055A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921A)
    - 135.0056A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921B)
    - 135.0057A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921C)
    - 135.0058A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921)
    - 135.0059A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921E)
    - 135.0060A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 921)
    - 135.0061A-135.0067A. Work order, timing strip, printing and negative cleaning report, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 922)
    - 135.0061A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922A)
    - 135.0062A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922B)
    - 135.0063A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922C)
    - 135.0064A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922)
    - 135.0065A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922E)
    - 135.0066A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922)
    - 135.0067A Edge number note, undated (Box 23, Folder 922G)
    - 135.0068A-135.0070A. Timing strip, printing and negative cleaning report, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 923)
    - 135.0071A-135.0076A. Timing sheet, timing strip, bag, printing negative cleaning report, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 924)
    - 135.0077A-135.0086A. Timer's listing, timing strip, bag, printing and negative cleaning report, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 925)
    - 135.0087A-135.0091A. Photo and envelope, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 926)
    - 135.0042A-135.0093A. Music cue sheets, note., undated (Box 23, Folder 927)
    - 135.0094A-135.0098A. 2 letters., undated (Box 23, Folder 928)
    - 135.0130A-135.0132A. Timing sheet, timing strip, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 929)
    - 135.0151A. Timing record, undated (Box 23, Folder 930)
    - 135.0163A-135.0134A Printing and Negative Cleaning report, color filter, instructions to timer., undated (Box 23, Folder 930A)
    - 135.0165A Printing and Negative Cleaning report, Packing slip, undated (Box 23, Folder 930B)
  - Subseries C: Production Materials, Film
    - Agreement between Jim Self and Frank Moore, undated (Box 23, Folder 931)
    - Bee Quiz, undated (Box 23, Folder 932)
    - "Curse of Isadora" New York Times article from November 23, 198x. Used as source material for Beehive, ca. 1980 (Box 23, Folder 933)
    - Fundraising and Budget, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 934)
    - Invoices, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 935)
    - Letter Re: Ellen van Schuylenburch, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 936)
    - Letter from Frank Moore to Jean, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 937)
    - Letterhead, undated (Box 23, Folder 938)
    - Lighting parameters, undated (Box 23, Folder 939)
    - Maeterlinck, Maurice. "La Vie Des Abeilles" approximate translation of paragraph from French to English, undated (Box 23, Folder 940)
    - Miscellaneous papers and drawings, undated (Box 23, Folder 941)
    - Notepad with dimensions, drawings and to do lists for costumes, undated (Box 23, Folder 942)
    - Primary Performance Group balance sheet and auditor's report. June 30, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 943)
    - Beehive Production Schedule Memo, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 944)
    - Beehive set instructions, undated (Box 23, Folder 945)
    - Source Materials (Box 23, Folder 946)
    - Special Thanks credits, undated (Box 23, Folder 947)
    - Storyboard, undated (Box 23, Folder 948)
    - To do lists, undated (Box 23, Folder 949)
  - Subseries D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theatre Production
    - Aggreements between Frank Moore, Scott Johnson and Jim Self. For "Beehive" ballet performance in Boston. February 7., undated (Box 23, Folder 950)
    - Boston Ballet Company, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 951)
    - Beehive Correspondence with Angiers, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 952)
    - Beehive correspondence with Boston, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 953)
    - Costume lists, Angiers to Boston, undated (Box 23, Folder 954)
    - Encouragement for Beehive, Boston, undated (Box 23, Folder 955)
    - Lighting Parameters (Box 23, Folder 956)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 957)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 958)
    - Modified Rep. Hanging plot. Boston Ballet, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 959)
    - Performance Schedule, Beehove 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 960)
    - Production bidsheet, Boston Ballet., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 961)
    - Projector information, sent by Boston Ballet to Frank Moore, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 962)
    - Receipts and financial information, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 963)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, undated (Box 23, Folder 964)
    - Scott Johnson, technical requirements, undated (Box 23, Folder 965)
    - "Special Note Regarding the Development of Beehive", undated (Box 23, Folder 966)
  - Subseries E: Promotional Materials
    - Invitation postcard to Beehive at CNCD d'Angers, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 967)
    - Invitations to Beehive at Theatre Municipal D'Angers, undated (Box 23, Folder 968)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 969)
    - Program from French Production at Centre National de Danse Contemporaine D'Angers, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 970)
    - Boston Ballet newspaper clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 971)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 972)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 973)
    - Boston Ballet Theatre bills, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 974)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 975)
    - Dance on Camera festival, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 976)
    - "Awards given in Dance" clipping regarding New York Dance and Performance Awards, undated (Box 23, Folder 977)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder data_value_missing_faa07fa845165a7a2dab216fd08aa95a)
  - Subseries F: Artifacts
    - Glass Panels, undated (Box 23, Folder 978)
    - Lighting scrims and foil material, undated (Box 23, Folder 979)
    - Model Flowers, undated (Box 23, Folder 980)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 23, Folder 981)
  - Subseries G: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    Scope and Contents
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Beehive (2005 Restoration), 1985; ID: 135.0274 (Box Shared Fales 131, Cd 135.0274)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:15:38
      Original Format: 16mm film
    - Beehive (1985 Dub), ID: 135.0288 (Box Shared Fales 150, Dvd 135.0288, Dvd 135.0287)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      TRT: 00:16:00
      Original Format: VHS
      Source ID: 135.0158
    - Beehive: Cornell Rough Rehearsal, 1991; ID: 135.0278 (Box Shared Fales 131, Cd 135.0278)
      TRT: 00:36:00
      Source ID: 135.0157
    - Beehive-- Ballet Excerpts, undated; ID: 135.0279 (Box Shared Fales 131, Cd 135.0279)
      Physical Characeteristics and Technical Requirements note
      TRT: 00:09:20
      Source ID: 135.0159
    - Beehive Excerpts, 1985 Angers Production, Dub by Frank Moore (Box Digitized Access Files, File 135.0156)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Source Format: VHS, Source ID: 135.0156, Duration: 18 min.
    - Primary Performance Group, Inc., "Beehive Ballet" (Box Digitized Access Files, File 135.0159)
      Source Format: VHS, Source ID: 135.0159, Duration: 9 min.
  - Subseries H: Film - Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    - "Beehive" (unrestored answer print), 1985 (Reel 135.0277)
      Physical Charateristics and Technical Requirements note
      Format: 16mm
      Total Footage: 587 ft.
- Series VI: Miller's Wife
  This series contains all production elements and materials relating to "The Miller's Wife" including film, video and audio elements, production notes, budgets, rental information, production and promotional materials as well as artifacts. Subseries A contains all production elements relating to the film. Items are organized by unique object identifcation numbers. Materials in Subseries B: Technical notations and Lab related paperwork relate to specific reels of film and are organized by unique object idenfication numbers. All other subseries are arrange alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Production Elements
    - Film Production Elements: 16mm b/w negative and 16mm color positive, 1987-1988 (Box 135.0133-135.0134)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988 (Box 135.0136-135.0138)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988 (Box ID: 135.0179)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988 (Box 135.0181-135.0254)
    - Film Production Elements, 1987-1988 (Box 135.0258-135.0260)
    - Video Production Element: Video Story Board #1, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0167 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0167)
      Video Recording, [20:00], JVC TC-20 SHG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Video Story Board #2, 1988-1990; ID: 135.0166 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0166)
      Video Recording, [20:00] TDK TC-20 HDX Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Dailies 10/22/87, ID: 135.0168 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0168)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Kodak Eastman EK T-60 HG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: "The Miller's Wife" -- 24" Silent Work Print, [undated]; ID: 135.0169 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0169)
      Video Recording, [30:00], Eastman Kodak EK T-30 HG Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: VHS Master "The Miller's Wife" with Scratchtrack, [undated]; ID: 135.0170 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0170)
      Video Recording, Maxell EX 120 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: DAT 1 Transfer "The Miller's Wife" 12/27/88, ID: 135.0175 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0175)
      Video Recording, [60:00], Ampex 197 BCA-60 Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: DAT 2 Transfer 12/27/88, ID: 135.0171 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0171)
      Video Recording, [10:00] Sony KCS-10XBR Video Cassette
    - Video Production Element: Master of Rough Cut "The Miller's Wife", [undated]; ID: 135.0172 (Box 23B, Media ID: 135.0172)
      Video Recording, [24:00], Eastman Kodak EK30 KCA Proffessional EP-930 Video Cassette